bollywoodfunda.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Bollywood Latest updates | Bollywood latest news, Hot Photos,Box Office, Movie Review, bollywoodFundaBollywood Latest updates | Bollywood latest news, Hot Photos,Box Office, Movie Review, bollywoodFunda

**Bollywood Funda**  has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:

**Information Automatically Logged  **  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. Your IP address or demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

**Cookies**  
Various methods are employed to gather this data. “Cookies” are used to distinguish and relate non personal data to individuals. These are “small strings of text” that are stored in browsers; cookies are not programs that can damage your computer. If you wish to stop the cookie functionality on your browser, you may do so.

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your login information so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

**Advertisers**  
We work with various third party advertising networks. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have access to this information.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Bollywood Hungama is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, opinion polls, and/or news available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We make every effort to maintain quality of service and prevent misuse.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [ _ **contact us.**_](http://bollywoodfunda.com/contact-us)
